Heat.
Heat. Heat.
[Music]
Heat. Heat. Heat.
Hey. Hey. Hey. Heat.
[Music]
Heat. Heat.
Heat. Heat. Heat.
[Music]
Heat. Hey, Heat.
Heat. Heat.
[Music]
Heat.
Heat. Heat.
[Music]
Welcome. Welcome Living Mana Church
family. It's so good to see you here at
Living Mana Church today on the Sabbath
day. We are so happy to see all of you.
Please put in the chat where you're
viewing from. And if this is your first
time, please put a one in the chat. If
you are visiting Living Mana Church for
the very first time, let us know because
we want to do give you a very special
welcome and we just want to welcome you
here to Living Mana Church again. We are
having quite the rainy wet Sabbath day
here in Northern North Alabama. But um I
was just reminded and brother Kashif
hopefully you're watching because I was
just reminded not to complain because he
just sent that yesterday uh to a prayer
group chat that we're both in but it's
the video says for one week don't
complain about anything. Instead switch
it around and say something positive. So
I had to say thank you Lord for all the
rain today because it's going to make
and yesterday and yesterday it was a lot
of rain yesterday and thunderstorms and
lightning and all of that. Um, thank you
for that because it's going to continue
to make Alabama, where we live, green
when the sun does come out again. That's
right. That's right. So, that's the
positive word. Thank you, Kashif, for
the encouragement. Yeah. And not to put
anybody on the edge, first of all,
welcome. And, uh, uh, welcome to Living
Mana Online Church. We're glad you are
with us today. Yes. And um not to put
anybody on edge, but yesterday during
the the rain and the storm that I think
was unexpected how heavy it was coming.
Um we actually lost some power. Wow. So
I didn't realize that. You know why? In
here. In here. Oh, really? So it's it's
raining actually right now. Right. It
started raining as soon as we were about
to go live. Pray for pray for studio.
Pray the pray that the power stays on.
Um, we've got backup power and
everything, but just uh so that we don't
have any issues. But again, we want to
welcome you. Glad that you're here. Let
me say greetings to We need to say
greetings. A lot of we got people from
all over. Welcome.
Welcome. Uh Jennifer Logan from
Tennessee, welcome. You're probably
maybe depending on what part of
Tennessee getting some of this rain too.
Um Robert Ray from Walaw Wala,
Washington, welcome to Living Mana
Church. Uh let's see. Leela Peterson
from North Carolina. Welcome to Living
Manage Church. Blessings, Joy from Barb,
sunny Barbados.
Rubbing it in. Welcome to Living Manage
Church uh here in rainy Huntsville,
Alabama. But we're happy to have you
here. More from Barbados. We are loved
in Barbados. We need to go visit
Barbados. Never been to that island. Uh
let's see. And we have Renee from our
from our old stomping ground, San Jose,
California. Welcome,
Renee. All right, we got Columbia, sunny
South
Carolina. That is um that's right.
That's that's Terry's hometown. I think
it's Colombia. Yeah, I know it's South
Carolina. I think right near there.
Right near Columbia, I believe. Um All
right. We have Feliz Abado from Marcela
Johnson. Happy Sabbath to you, too,
Marcella. Um, let's see. Regina from
Brooklyn, New York. More, of course.
Ayana, our church member from Trinidad
and
Tobago. Western Washington. Oh, of
course. Carrie, good to see you. Tell
your family hello for us. There's Walaw
Wala. I thought I said Walaw Wala up at
the beginning, but
welcome. And we got Phoenix. And I don't
know if you see Barbara from Fricksburg,
Virginia. Oh, Barbara. Hi. From our se
our our second home for sure. We spend
lots and lots of time there. We'll be
there shortly. Um, let's
see. Yeah, there's just lots of people.
All right, I got Queens, New York.
Esther from Queens, New York. Good to
see you here. Welcome, Jerry from
Rochester, New York. We got Queens in in
the city and we've got Rochester. What?
Way up in in upper up um what do you
guys call it? Upstate. Upstate New York.
Upstate New York. That's what New
Yorkers call it? Upstate. All right.
Welcome here. MNA from Tacoma,
Washington. Welcome here to Living
Matter Church. We are happy to see all
of
you.
Um
okay. Happy Sabbath. Whoa. Whoa. It went
fast here. Martha from Lebanon. Is that
the Lebanon the church or Lebanon the
country? Because there's a church
Lebanon in New York. Let's find out
because Yeah. Tell us if that if that's
the church. Isn't that where you got
baptized? That's where I was baptized
the first time. The first time. No,
actually, actually, no, no, no, no.
That's where you were introduced. That's
where you and the group went the first
time. That's Then we were baptized at
Kingsboro. So, Beirut, Lebanon. Wow. Oh,
okay. Wow. Well, welcome. Welcome. Is
this your first time? I feel like it's
the first time I ever said Lebanon.
So, I need a one. But we're so happy to
have you, Martha from Beirut, Lebanon.
So happy to have you. Please let us know
if this is your first time. Uh, then we
have Janice from BISE. Welcome.
All right. I love it. We are We are It's
so funny. Some Sabbaths were more heavy
on the international side and then some
Sabbaths were more heavy on the on the
mainland or in America side or North
America. So, Oh, yeah. Very. Yeah,
that's cool. Um yeah, first time. Well,
welcome. Just to let you know, gota
gonna give my little spill for you,
Martha. And everybody, please welcome
Martha. She's here for the very first
time. And this is an 100% online church.
And we have we are not just here on
Sabbath, but we are here during the
week. So, I just want to tell you a
little bit about that. We have Mental
Health Monday programming and it's
hosted by myself and Dr. White. He is a
psychiatrist and I'm a licensed
therapist and we cover all things mental
health. We also have True Health Tuesday
where we have two uh doctors and a
licensed uh nutritionist where they talk
about um how you can live a healthy life
and and things that you can do for your
health to better your health. We have
power Wednesdays on Wednesday where our
prayer team leads out in a prayer
service that is beautiful. Um, on
Thursday we have our associate, our
young adult pastor who leads out in a
program on Thursday. So Martha, please
stay with us because I'm going to tell
you how you can sign up to get more
information about living man church and
stay connected in the divine worship
service. So we are happy that you are
are here with us. Um, and we are hope
you come back. So definitely Amen. sign
up to get those alerts. Yeah. uh your
shirt. I was That's why I was turning
this way. I was like and I saw you. I
saw you. I was like shirt uh but seek
first his kingdom.
The whole scripture is down here. Okay.
Matthew 6:33. But seek ye first the
kingdom of God. Uh first but the but
first this the top part is is important.
Um the whole verse is important.
Um, this stood out to me. Um, just
because this is
something, this key phrase first, when
you
first feel emotions of anger, seek God.
When you first feel anxiety, seek God,
which is fear. When you first have bouts
of sadness, which can lead into
depression, seek God first. Let that be
the first thing that you do. Imagine
yourself turning to God, laying your
emotions and your issues just like
almost even laying I mean I you could
imagine how you want to imagine, but I
could see myself falling on on on
Jesus's lap, you know, just like I'm
bringing this to you. I need help.
Please help me to feel better. My
emotions are too strong. They're trying
to pull me in the wrong direction. Take
a deep seek God first and then take a
deep breath and calm down and think from
here. Give him everything and then make
your moves. Don't just make moves just
off of the feeling and that emotion
because you're gonna make the wrong
move, say the wrong thing, do the wrong
thing, seek God first, breathe, and then
do what you have to do. Y So, amen.
That's the encouragement for today.
Amen. Amen. So, you also wanted to talk
about your upcoming sermon for Yeah.
Yes. So, um, actually,
uh, today is, and we haven't done this
in quite a while, but today is
Evangelism Sabbath. Okay. And I know we
typically do Evangelism Sabbath at the
end of the month, but over the last
several months, until this year, yeah,
happened. It's just, you know, a lot has
been going on, which most of you know.
So, um, so even though this is the first
Sabbath of the month, um, I decided to
do an evangelism Sabbath. Now, um this
evangelism Sabbath subject today is
you've heard me talk about it before. I
am going to be talking about um the
overmastering delusion
um of Satan appearing as Christ. But
every time I've presented it, I've
presented it using today. Oh, okay.
Yeah. every time I pre presented it, I
presented it using uh quotes from the
spirit of prophecy and I've mostly
spoken to, you know, an Adventist
audience. So today
um I'll be presenting it for the first
time strictly from scripture. I'm
excited.
So, and here's why that's relevant
because put a one in the chat if you've
been to um you know, if you've been to
our evangelistic series, seen our
evangelistic series. Sat Adventist in
general. Yeah. The Adventist evangel
evangelistic series. I know for for me
I've been to many Yeah. I have I don't
think I have ever
seen a
presentation on Satan appearing as
Christ.
Not a not a whole presentation. It it
might have been it might have been
mentioned, but I don't know. You you
tell me if you've seen one where you
know the whole thing is about Satan
appearing as Christ. I know. You know
what's weird? Yeah. for me because you
know I was raised my story is so
different than your story but I was
raised Adventist and
um I vaguely I can't seem to remember
sitting in a series hearing that but
because my like grandfather and
grandmother well my grandfather really
was such a deep studyer of the word and
would always do our worships and you
know closing and ending the Sabbath and
all that stuff it and I just feel I like
that I feel like I've heard that before.
That wasn't new to me. That wasn't a new
concept to me. Now,
but your grandfather didn't do an
evangelistic series, did he? No, he
didn't. But I'm just saying that we
could Well, not that I know of. So, so I
mean I I know that people understand it
and and people believe it and may have
always believed so, but what I'm saying
is that
as a presentation, no, right from in in
an evangelistic series.
Um I've never seen it. I know that up
until, you know, a few, in fact, in my
last um full evangelistic series, I know
I didn't cover it because at that time I
didn't have that, you know what I'm
saying? That that understanding that I
do now.
So
I think today's presentation is going to
be special in that it is going to be
presented strictly from the scripture
because I think for a lot of people that
they might be like well I can you know I
can talk about that but I would prove
that from the word right. I could go to
Yeah, I could go to Spirit of Prophecy
and show, hey, she says this, here, she
says this here, she says this. But how
do we how do we teach this as part of an
evangelistic series from the Bible using
the Bible only? So, and that's what we
want to do for everything. And that's
what we want to do for that's what we do
for everything. I know that's but I
almost an important principle for
everyone else to really really
um study in that way. Yeah. Yeah. And
it's almost as if because we have way
too many challenges to be like, "Oh, you
guys are Ellen White heavy. You can only
do that through Ellen White." But to
shut all that noise down, you have to be
able to present from the Bible. And
maybe it hasn't been presented because
people are like, "Well, it's not really
revealed in the scripture, but you can
clearly see it in spirit of prophecy."
Now I believe it is clearly revealed in
scripture. So we're going to be looking
at that today. So again we every
evangelism Sabbath we say make sure that
you share you know particularly with
those who may not be uh familiar with uh
with Adventism. Share this with
everybody and share this on your social
media. Yeah. Because this is needed for
Adventists for non-adventists for
everybody. Yeah. So as I preach today it
again it will be directed towards it'll
be as if you know nothing. Right. I'm
going to be speaking to um you know,
hopefully I'm going to be directing this
message just like every other evangelism
Sabbath to those who may have never
heard these things before and it's going
to be straight from the Bible. So again,
make sure you share this link, share it
with uh with people that you would like
to see. This is going to be an important
message today. It's going to be simple.
Believe it or not, it is so simple in
the scripture that it's it's amazing
that it hasn't been taught. Mhm. Um at
least on a scale that I believe that it
should be. But um anyway, make sure you
share the link. Okay. Um so I'm excited
about that. And uh as I was putting it
together yesterday, I was just like,
"Wow, this is coming together like
really, really, really nicely. Something
even some things I had not seen before."
Um so anyway, yeah, I knew you were
working on something. You were very
quiet. Yeah. Yeah, very quiet. It was
just away, tucked away quietly. And for
Sour School, we're kind of actually
keeping it along the same lines. We're
going to be talking about developments,
prophetic developments that have been uh
happening over the last few days. Few
days
um and weeks and months and actually
years. So, yes. And happy Sabbath,
daughter. I thought that was our
daughter. I just saw her name.
So, um, so yeah, we are doing that and
we do have because we sent out an alert
that it's question and answer Sabbath,
which it is, but we decided that the
last we decided we're going to do
something different. It Yeah. So, we're
going to try to see if we can mix the
two. But, if you have questions on the
subject we're about to talk about,
that's where your questions are going to
be directed to. I do have religious.
We're gonna be talking about questions.
Um we're gonna be talking about the
merging of church and state. Um
particularly with what's been happening
um with the religious liberty commission
that has just been formed on Thursday uh
on Thursday into law. Uh and we're going
to be focusing on that because
we believe it is very significant.
Um and we want to we want to talk about
it. So okay, that's what we're going to
be discussing. And if you got questions
along that line. Yes. And I'm going to
answer chat.
Two of the mental health questions I got
and then we're going to jump into this.
Yeah. Is that okay? That's okay. Yeah.
So you pray for us. So let's pray.
Heavenly Father, we ask Lord that as we
uh get into the Sabbath school today,
Lord, that you would please just speak
through us, Lord, that um your word will
be made clear, Lord, that this subject
will be made clear. And um Lord uh help
us to realize that we are uh truly
living in in
um monumental times. Lord um open our
eyes that we may see and uh we thank you
Lord for giving us this opportunity to
worship together in Jesus name we pray.
Amen.
Amen. Amen. So let's see.
got a few mental health. Well, I'm just
gonna I'm just gonna answer two quickly
so we can jump. And as you're doing
that, Janice, this just actually know
that um I'm going to be beginning a
series here
soon. Um and I'm going to call the
series CrossFit.
Uh,
and the series will demonstrate how the
cross fits as the center of all
doctrines in the Bible.
So, you're such a play on words. Such a
play on words.
Yeah, you're funny. So, crossfit. Yeah,
crossfit. How does a cross fit with the
Sabbath? How does a cross fit with
hellfire? How does a cross fit with the
state of the dead? All of the things.
How does a cross fit with the
investigative judgment? And what I want
to demonstrate is that the cross is the
center
of all of our teachings. Yes. And in
order for the teaching to be rightly
understood, it's got to be seen in light
of the cross. So, I may actually be
doing this as an evangelistic
um as a
full
evangelistic series
on Sabbath morning, four living men,
right? State of the dead one one topic.
But this is he has to do that. But this
is this this will be on Sabbath. So,
this would be a series of sermon. We
just finished the nine uh essentials and
so um look out for that and and it will
be coming be really good very soon. Very
soon. Okay. Okay.
So Okay. I have a question and and the
question says the Bible says that we
should that we should esteem that we
should not esteem that we should not
esteem ourselves better than other than
other themselves. Uh what is the
difference between esteeming others and
people pleasing? In both someone else
let's see what is in in both someone
else whatever is
given first
consideration. Yes. Okay, that's how
they worded it, but I think I understand
the question. So, this happens a lot of
time. First of all, Dr. White and I did
a three-part series, three-part on
mental health Mondays on people
pleasing. We were going off of the book,
The Disease to Please. And this
question, we actually addressed it there
as well. And this happens, this is asked
a lot um especially in the Christian
circles because when we're saying, you
know what, you need to set boundaries
and you need to not just be um um an
addicted people pleaser. Um because
meaning and people will say, well, isn't
it good to do nice things for other
people? It is good to do nice things for
other people and God does call us to do
that. But in the Christian circle with a
people pleaser, they have a hard time
setting boundaries and they have a hard
time saying the beautiful no. And the
verse that this person was talking about
um the in context that verse it's
talking about not um esteeming yourself
better like oh I'm prettier than her. I
have a better uh job than him or um you
know I'm just a better person than this
person. like you're not supposed to
um try to make yourself seem better than
other people. Um and so people pleasing
is different than what that scripture is
talking about. Um again, it is not being
able to say no because you're afraid
that people are not going to like you.
They're not going to want you if you say
no. And the only way that you can get
them to like you is to do these things.
So you're not even coming from a healthy
place. You're coming from a place of I'm
trying to get you to like me, so I'm
going to do everything and I'm and I'm
scared that you're not going to like me,
so I'm going to do all these things. I
don't even really want to do it, but I'm
going to do it because I want you to
like me. And so it's not the right
motives. Um, and so it that's why it is
different from that verse that you that
you asked about. Okay. Do you have
anything you want to say about that? No,
no, no. You I think you Okay. got that
good. Okay. So, there was one other
[Music]
question and I have to find it really
quickly here. Um, there were a lot of
actually mental health questions today.
So, someone is
asking that's that same
question. Oh, boy. All right. Someone
basically I'll have to paraphrase it
because I can't just pull it up right
here, but they're basically was was
saying that they've been to therapy a
lot. they've done all different types of
therapy and they're not having um
success. I mean, she had mentioned a lot
of different things and she's still just
dealing with a lot of stuff and she was
asking and she was interested in
ketamine and I don't know um if a lot of
people may not be familiar with what
ketamine is and it is actually uh
something they use um when you like for
anesthesia when you're going into
surgery. It's a part of that. it can be
a part of that in a much higher dose.
And then they have mo recently in in the
in the last I don't know I don't know
the date actually so I shouldn't make it
seem like it's just the last few years.
I don't know how long they've actually
been using ketamine. Not it hasn't been
that long for mental health but they are
starting to use ketamine for mental
health. Let's just say in the last 10
years I think it's safe to say that um
on certain in certain situations or
people can go and have that treatment
done. Um and this person was asking what
I think about it. So I'll give my
opinion that
um where I have spoken to some people
who say that they do get relief for some
of their depression and anxiety and
different mental health issues. Um
it it's like it's you have to keep going
back uh to do that because they can't
seem to
um it almost makes you dependent upon
that. So I don't want to it is a drug
and I know people take anti-anxiety and
anti-depress depressants and all of
those type of things. Um
but with ketamine you go
into I want to say a trip. When I say a
trip, like you're literally you're
you're high. I mean, you're high. You're
you're I don't want to say hallucinating
quite. You're not quite hallucinating,
but you're going in different places in
your brain that you don't go to just
like what we would do right here in our
natural state. Like it literally takes
you into different places in your brain
and you start to see things different
and get a different perspective and then
you come out with that understanding.
So, I
um I'm not a I'm not a supporter of it.
Obviously, people can see that I'm not a
supporter of it
because I don't know what's going to
happen, you know, in that I call it a
trip because you're going into a place
that you can't go to unless you're high
on that drug, right? Um and so um
anything could happen there and you
could get a very not a good perspective
at all and then there's
no therapist or somebody there to help
you process that in a healthy way. Does
that make sense? It could make it worse.
But there are people who who who do
that. Um and it's not cheap. It's
expensive to do that. So I don't promote
it. But um people have their freedom of
choice to do what they want. So,
anyways, that's ketamine. Okay. All
right. So, those are the two questions
that I'm going to answer. And now we're
going to jump in. If you have questions
about what we're about to present now,
please put it in the chat as we're
presenting. Yeah. Okay. So, um we are
and you know, someone
just I'm
gonna Yeah, I saw a question here.
Um, should we as Adventists be
protesting the coming together of church
and state and also the inhumane
treatment of migrants, those with darker
skin and all and uh all the rights
people are
losing? So, this is kind of a a heated
not a heated this is a a firecracker
question, but it's a good question. But
it's a good question.
Um, let me just say it this way.
when they start coming
[Music]
for Christians, which the Bible
prophesies.
Um, I
think we will appreciate people standing
up against the ill treatment of those
who keep the commandments of God and
have the faith of Jesus. Right. Right.
or maybe they're not even keeping the
commandments of God. But we should treat
others the way that we would want to be
treated ourselves. So how how I think we
absolutely should be protesting that
which is
um which is unjust.
So the argument of whether this is
actually unjust or not, I'm not even
addressing that. But if there is
something that is unjust then God's
people I believe should raise the voice
in defense of others just as we would
want people to raise their voice in
protest if something you know
persecution were to happen um towards us
right so do unto others as you would
have them do unto you right treat others
it's as you would want to be treated and
I'm Sure, if some one of y'all got
arrested today for something that you
didn't do, right, you would certainly
want uh other voices
uh speaking up. So again, this is not
addressing what is actually just or
unjust. It it is addressing if the thing
is unjust, then our voices should be
raised. Um, how however we we we protest
because we are Protestants, right? And
Protestants protest.
Um, we we we ought to do so. There's
nothing not Christian about protesting.
Yeah. It's a Christian thing to do.
Yeah. Um, and in a nice way, right? And
um we're to do that within the context
of the three angels messages, right?
We're to do that in the context of the
everlasting gospel, uh that's always our
context. That's always our context. So,
um with that said, with that said, uh
let's talk about what's been happening.
Yeah.
Lately. And I'm sure you're going to
read something from there. I probably
you should just read it, but I just saw
it like Thursday. I guess it happened
Thursday afternoon. I didn't see it.
Yeah. Been until Thursday evening.
Um scrolling on social media. And so
yeah, news alert. So yeah, absolutely.
Um
we so a religious
uh committee was just formed a
department a department that is designed
to
uh again root out
anti-Christian
bias. Um, and it supposedly says in
their wording to protect religious
liberty, right?
Because it's in the constitution. Didn't
know it was not being protected, but
yeah. So, this is But then, okay.
So, um, you know, as I was s as I was
looking at this and there's a lot of
people online talking about, you know,
what significance this has. And one
thing I want to I want to say right off
the bat
is that I believe religious
liberty is going to be the
umbrella under which the prophetic
um the prophetic warnings that we have
seen in the scriptures are going to
unfold. Mhm. In other words, the Bible
talks about
um the the union of the beasts from the
earth and the beasts from the sea and
the dragon and that they're going to end
up enforcing religious worship, but it
is going to be under the guise of
religious liberty. Mhm. And I don't
think it's coincidence that we're
hearing all this talk about religious
liberty. And in my estimation,
um, religious
liberty is
being manipulated. Yes. It is being
distorted
into something that it it it is not.
Mhm. And this distorted view of
religious liberty, I think we're seeing
that unfold before us right now. Mhm. Um
I did a we did a message, I think it was
our Friday night a couple of weeks ago
where we were talking about persecution
in America versus persecution around the
world in regards of Christianity. Do it
together. You did it. Are you sure you
weren't on with me? Not
Friday night. I was I was it a f I was
just So it may have been my It may have
been my sermon. It may have been I don't
think it was your sermon, but it was the
one. Anyway, so so basically I was
showing how um how around the world
there is actual persecution, right, of
Christians happening around the world.
People are literally being killed,
right? Mhm. And here in America, our
religious persecution is I am being
forced I can't send my kids to um the
government won't pay for me to send my
kids to private school. I'm being
persecuted, right? Or I I was forced to
bake a cake. I was forced to bake a
cake. Now, I'm not saying that these
things don't effect have an effect on
Thank you, Lisa. Yeah. have an effect on
this was a sermon have an effect on
people you know on their livelihood and
things of that nature. Um I'm not saying
persecute I mean I'm not saying that
Christians in America do not face
uh you know our constitution has
protected us very well absolutely very
well and that's why
America has done so well in that realm
yeah and in cases where other countries
have not in cases where your religious
liberty is being trampled upon you have
recourse in other countries you don't
really have recourse If they it is what
it is and that's it. You protect our
Sabbath rights are protected. I mean if
if I mean you can
you can you can take it to the court.
You can you can Yeah. If they get rid of
you because you you know they're
discriminating against you because
you're you won't work on Sabbath. You
can fight that. Yeah. Yeah. So, so the
idea then that uh a committee needs to
be formed to protect religious
liberty in America, the Constitution
does that. The Constitution already does
that. Now, interestingly
enough, the
the we're told in prophecy
that the this these liberties will be
taken away. And I think the ironic thing
is that they're gonna be taken away
under the guise of religious liberty,
right? Because when you look to
Christian nationalism, their
argument of religious liberty is
actually religious favoritism.
Right. Right. Christians should have the
liberty. I was not Muslims. Thank you. I
was just going to say that. Not should
the American
tax
dollars pay for. Okay. If it's paying
for Christians to send their kids to
Christian school, then it should pay for
Muslims to send their kids to to Muslim
schools and for Buddhists the same. And
for Jews, the same. And you know, it's
But that's not what they're talking
about. No. No, that's not what they're
talking about. they are this in fact the
very fact that this um religious
committee has been formed and so I
believe there's two of them there's the
one that was uh there's there's one
headed up by Paula White
well okay and this is something new okay
yeah this is something new that came out
on Thursday because the one I think the
one that's headed up by Paula White is
just a religious
um group of pastors and religious
leaders that
um that are for the president or for the
White House. Do you see what I'm saying?
Like but this is assigned into law
religious liberty. Yeah.
So again you
guys religious liberty is being I'm
going to use this word is is being
prostituted. Well brother Kashie said
yes there's two. So yeah, if if there's
different if it's different than what I
said, brother Kashe, put a one in the
chat and you might, you know, so you can
explain and you can explain in the chat
too. Yeah. Or, you know, put you can put
the the the the two there are two
different uh names and this just
slipping my mind right now, but one was
done um as an executive order, I believe
it was, right? Um and then uh this one
is a new one. I want and I want to get
into this for more. We're going to get
into this shortly, but because if it's
different than what I said, I'm not as
familiar with the Paul White thing then.
Yeah.
So, religious liberty is being
prostituted. It is being manipulated.
Mhm. Um the understanding of
it
is and I think we've even seen it in the
church that in the church there's now
you know well what really is religious
liberty right
right it's it's
it's there's a lot of confusion now I
think Satan has brought in confusion
about what religious liberty actually is
even inside the church, but we're not
going there today.
Um, so let's talk about
um before you take a deep. Yeah, this
question keeps coming up. People are
people are asking more than one saying
like like what your thoughts are about
uh the picture from last night. We're
not We're Yeah, we're just hold on.
Okay. Just hold on. Okay.
We're We're going in order here. Okay.
So, I'm going to pull it up. I'm gonna
see if I can pull up on my computer and
just read
uh let's see. Okay. So uh this is
from here's one article and it's being
written all about all over but Trump
creates a religious liberty commission
on national day of prayer and it says
President Donald Trump signed an
executive order Thursday morning
establishing a presidential commission
on religious liberty during a White
House Rose Garden event in honor of the
National Day of Prayer.
The commission panel will include
members like US housing secretary uh Ben
Carson, talk TV show host Phil McGra,
and Texas Lieutenant Governor Dan
Patrick, who will also serve as the
chair. Now, I know what all I know what
y'all are thinking. What do you think
about? Don't ask me what I think about.
I'm not even going to mention that. All
right, we're just going to leave that
be. Here's what I do want to show you,
though. Who is Texas Lieutenant Governor
Dan Patrick? I'm going to ask uh our
broadcast team if you can go ahead and
play
um the video
uh to show who Lieutenant Governor Dan
Patrick is, who is going to be chairing
this new committee. So, let's see if we
can we can play that that video.
Louisiana public schools are now
required to display the Ten Commandments
in all classrooms. Republican Governor
Jeff Landry signed that bill into law
today. The legislation specifies the
text must be printed in quote large and
easily readable font. Louisiana is the
only state with this mandate. Legal
challenges of that law are expected.
Well, last year, Texas lawmakers tried
to pass a similar measure, but it
failed.
Okay. Um, and I don't I don't know if
Lieutenant Governor Dan Patrick was
mentioned in the clip. I think he was.
If he was, if he was
not, this is the
governor in Texas.
Yes. Who is seeking to in fact, do we
have another clip? Can you show Can you
guys show the
first clip? I don't know if it's if it's
not of Lieutenator uh of uh the
lieutenant governor. Um you don't have
to show it. If it is, I want you to put
it
up. Okay? I don't think it is. We'll
just go ahead and I'm just going to tell
you to go ahead and look up who this is.
This is the same governor who is seeking
to have the Ten Commandments placed in
all the schools in Texas.
Not you guys. And I'm sure prayer in
school. Prayer in school and the Ten
Commandments in school.
Just think that through for a moment,
y'all.
Just think that through for a moment. So
remember some time back um a few months
back we did a presentation on this
movement to get the ten commandments
into public schools and we looked at I
believe it was uh either North Carolina
or South Carolina. We looked at Texas
was one of the places we looked at.
Arizona, how there is this movement, um,
a united effort, might I add, to bring
the Ten Commandments back into the
public school into the public school
system. And Lieutenant Governor, uh, Dan
Patrick is the guy that was leading this
mission out in Texas. He is
now the
chair of this religious liberty
commission. Oklahoma's one of them as
well. Yes, Regina.
Think that through. You guys,
the guy who's trying to get the Ten
Commandments into all the schools in
Texas is now heading up this commission.
Now, I don't And by the way, he's trying
to get the Ten Commandments in all the
schools based upon religious liberty
arguments.
We should have the
liberty. Christians should have the
liberty to
post the Ten
Commandments. As Michelle just said, the
problem isn't with the Ten Commandments.
The problem is that the ten commandments
are are supposed to be posted in our
hearts, right?
And when you talk about legalism, I kind
of I'm kind of going off going a little
bit off here. And whose version? Because
And whose version? Does the Catholics?
Yeah. They got a different version. They
have a different version.
Legalism. This is the definition of
legalism, you guys. We're going to make
it legal. We're going to make it a law
that the Ten Commandments should be
written in the into
government. The very same people, mind
you, who say the Ten Commandments have
been done away with, you don't need them
on your heart. You don't need them in
your heart. We're under a new law now.
Legalism is literally we're going to
force you. And this is the beginning of
that, you guys. This is what we're
seeing. What are the odds that the guy
who is seeking to implement the Ten
Commandments into public schools in
Texas is the guy Trump chooses to head
up this national
religious
committee to protect religious to
protect religious liberty. And what I
read and it kind of goes with kindness
word. I we must have grown up at the
same time because uh kindness kind I
said kindness word. Kindness wins said
um how do we as SDAs get so mixed up?
When I was a kid we were against prayer
in schools and the ten commandments
being in public schools. And so I was
just saying I grew up around the same
time. I mean you know I believed the
same thing when I was young and still
do. But um I was going to say because I
read the what was signed into law from
the White House website. So it wasn't
misinformation, not from somewhere else.
It's from their website,
whitehouse.gov. Um and so the religious
liberty areas because they feel like
Christians have been discriminated
against because they haven't been able
to have those Christian things, prayer
and school, ten commandments on the
wall. So, they've been discriminated
against and this specifically is going
to be able to bring that back in along
with Christian organizations being
discriminated against from getting
government funding for different things.
They feel like they've been and yeah and
so that and they try
well they try to rewrite the
constitution that it means something
different uh the separation of church
and state. So that was the next thing
that that's not what our right founding
fathers were. Um and so Trump actually
said this and it's unfortunate but you
know to
even mention the name Trump people going
to be like oh you're getting political.
So and I I I don't understand you know
why that is. But I'm just saying this is
what's happening right? Prophecy yes the
Bible's political. Yeah. Prophecy has to
do with politics. It has to do with how
politics is going to merge with
Christianity, right? So if you want to
say that's political, then you know then
okay. Um uh that's what it is. Like
Harry said too, she said, "We need a
study about at Jones. We need a study on
Absolutely." Yeah. So uh who defended
religious liberty showed what religious
liberty actually is. Yeah. And it's
unfortunate that today in our church we
we've got this mixed up idea of what
religious liberty is, right?
And unfortunately, I think we're getting
it from the very people who we see are
twisting the definition and the meaning
and the sacredness of religious liberty.
Right. Because religious liberty is a
sacred thing. Yes. Right. Um
so, so
again, you have this this talk of well
there there's really no such thing as
separation of church and state. And you
know they said that oh you know well um
they were joking when they said you know
when they said that it was it was said
as a joke but they only other people
aren't joking fled Europe came over you
know fled persecution wasn't a joke.
Yeah. Well that's what I'm saying. Well
what I'm saying is they're saying that
when that was said a few days ago by by
the president you're saying that our
fathers were joking. Okay. Okay. Got it.
Um,
so the fact is that there are people
literally saying there is no such thing
as separation of church and state. Now
I've heard that before. For those of you
who have
said that uh, you know, uh, the
Adventist church and you know this Ellen
White, she's a false prophet and
whatever, whatever. Mh. How do you
explain How do you
explain
how what we're seeing now
was said back then in the 1800s? Yeah.
Warning after warning after warning.
This is coming. This is going to
happen. We haven't seen it in American
history. No. The way we're seeing it
now. There has never been a time like
this.
They for the most part the Constitution
has been very well protected and it has
not tried to be tinkered with in the way
that it's trying to be messed with now.
So, this is significant. I want to I'm
going to show another clip
and let's go ahead and just show that
picture.
uh and I want to talk about the
significance of this picture. So, as we
know,
um the Catholic Church is now looking
for a new
pope. And
um this
picture, the picture that was posted
last night, uh on yesterday, I believe
it was at some point in time. Not sure
when. like 10:07 p.m.
Now,
um, this picture is very
significant. This picture is very
significant. No, Donald Trump is not
going to be the next pope. No, he that's
that's just that's funny. He's not going
to be the next
pope. However,
but why would he put that picture out?
However, this is absolutely
significant because in this one
picture, what you
have
is a snapshot of Revelation chapter
13. The first
beast is the papacy. The second
beast is apostate
Protestantism, meaning Protestantism or
Christianity that is not real
Christianity.
In this picture, you have those
elements, church and state mingle
together. Now again, Yeah. Yeah. Uh
Nicole, a picture is worth 1,260 words.
I love the way you put that. That
picture is worth
1,260 words. Um,
this amalgamation that we've been saying
is coming of church and
state,
religio political power. Revelation 13,
the first beast uh, from the sea.
Revelation 13:11, the the second beast
from the earth merging
together. Even though I believe that
picture was was a joke, it is highly
significant. Like there's a lot of I've
seen I've seen a I saw this on regular
social media and there's a lot of I saw
Catholics saying this is this is very
disrespectful and not funny. like it's
they just whether you know we know in
prophecy the role of the the system of
the Catholic Church and all of that.
This is still their leader who just
passed away.
That is like no empathy. No. Like that's
just And you're supposed and you're the
president of the United States that I
can't I don't even know the number of
how many Yeah. millions of Catholics
there are or just I know there's a
billion around the world. I mean, it's
just so um I have my therapist thoughts
on why he would do something like that.
So, and again, like for me, I'm not even
talking about him I know as a person or
what he did. I'm simply saying that the
I was I was saying it wasn't nice. Yeah,
it Yeah, sure. for the timing. I mean,
right, it's not something funny at all.
It shouldn't It shouldn't be a a joke in
in any way, shape, or form.
But but the fact
is how there is no way to deny the
prophetic significance of this this
image. Now again I'm not saying the
image is prophetic. Not at all. The
picture is prophetic. I'm not all I'm
saying is that it
is while while a joke it is highly
significant. Mhm. Um, how many of you
remember Saul? The story of
Saul and
Samuel. Um, Saul.
What part of Saul? Yeah. Saul and his
rebellion against God. Right. They
wanted a king. Right. Right. Uh, that
king was Saul.
Um, and
Saul the Saul becoming a
king paved the
way for all the other kings which paved
the way for the
rise the fall of Israel and the rise of
Babylon. Right? So when the people asked
for a
king, that's what paved the way for them
eventually to be destroyed by Babylon.
But there's something significant about
Saul.
Um when Saul when God actually
left Saul, it was because Saul had done
something,
right? So Saul had been told to wait for
Samuel. I'm going to read it in 1 Sam
1st Samuel chapter 13 verse 8. He tried
seven days according to the set time
that Samuel had appointed. But Samuel
came not to Gilgag and the people were
scattered from him. And Saul said,
"Bring hither a burnt offering to me and
peace offering." And he offered the
burnt
offering. And this when when Samuel
finally
came, he was rebuked for what he had
done. So here's the
significance.
Saul who was a
king took upon
himself the
prerogatives of the priesthood.
And in doing that in that moment what
you saw
joined was
for on actually doing what the current
Sabbath school is talking about. That's
what Betina Whitehead said. Okay. Yeah.
Yeah. We did hear somebody else doing it
this morning too but yeah. So in Saul in
that moment you had a combination of
church and state
and this was a rebellion against God. It
is so significant. This is the same
thing with Constantine.
In
Constantine, you had a union of church
and
state.
And in
this under this
administration, and I guess there's no
other way for me to say it without being
accused of being political, but that's
just going to have to be it. Then under
this administration, there is a push.
There is a Saulike spirit. There is a
Constantine-like spirit within the
administration, right? An attempt. So,
I'm not pointing out one individual. I'm
simply saying under
this
administration and the Christians who
support it, there is a push to merge
church and state together to do away
with the distinguishing with the
distinguishing with the separation of
church and state and it's all happening
before our eyes.
And I have to say
that in a sense I'm I'm kind of happy
that I'm not kind of happy I'm happy
that more people are talking about it
now because it's getting to the point
where it is so obvious that to ignore it
is is now being seen as as
absolutely how can you even ignore it?
You may not have wanted to talk about it
before. you may have wanted to downplay
it before,
but now it's getting to the place where
yeah, we we're now having to
say
even even though you may not have wanted
to, man, I didn't want it to be under
this, you know, admin. And I'm not
saying that this administration is going
to bring in a Sunday law. Please
remember that. We have been very
consistent on that because certain
things have to have to happen. A Sunday
law will not be dependent
upon any human being. No. And upon any
administration, it is
dependent on the overmastering delusion
taking the whole world captive. Yes.
What I am saying is that what we see
happening now is
definitely Satan setting the stage and I
believe even God allowing us to
see that this thing is is it's happening
the way we have always taught that it
would happen and it the the the fruit is
ripe. I like what Christian um Toronto
said um saying so many non-adventists
are seeing this truth. Yep. Because it's
it's just such a while while so many
Adventists are just like but No, that's
sad.
But the pro there's also a shaking and
that I mean look the Bible the majority
of God's people
are out there are out there in the
fallen churches are out there you know
in other religious systems are out there
not even believing you know right now
yes but when they see this stuff coming
to pass they're like wait a minute when
they see this stuff happening Mariah we
see you said I'm not an Adventist but
this is indeed the truth praise
Amen. Praise God. Praise God. When you
see this, and remember like when I'm
watching secular people beginning to
lift their voices against
this union of church and state, it is
absolutely mind-blowing because a lot of
these people don't even believe in a
Bible, right? Do you know how shocked
they would be to know that the book that
they think is fake, the book that they
think is not real,
actually
foretold the very thing we are seeing
now? Mhm.
How do you explain a book that is this
old, as old as a
Bible, literally accurately
foretelling what is going on
right
now. And again, it's sad to say that,
you know, for many people, screenshot
Mariah's last
um I gotta screenshot that we got to
save this anyway. I guess this will be
in the chat because guys, I don't know
if you're not if you're watching on your
TV and you're not on a on your phone to
see comments. Mariah, who we're so happy
that is here. She's not Adventist, but
she's saying to you Adventists and to
all of us, Adventist, why are you not
proclaiming
boldly? Like, that's a mic drop. If we
could just let's just sit with that.
That That's a rebuke. That's a rebuke.
It's a mic drop. If there ever was one,
if there ever was one, that is it right
there. Because I I always say we should
have been the first ones way
back way back we should have been
lifting the warning voice saying look
guys this is coming this is coming this
is happening this is eight years ago was
easily seen 10 years ago easily seen 12
years ago we could have easily seen this
but by and large so many people were
silent and now here we are and again
this is not saying again we're here now
and it's going to happen now. That's not
what we're saying. We're simply saying
as Adventists, we have always taught
this. We've all we've always understood
this. But but something got in the mix.
And we and we still just haven't gotten
this into every nation, tongue, and
people. But by God's grace, that's going
to change. And that's going to happen.
How powerful it has to happen. How
powerful would it be for the world who
is now really really
like what's going on for them to go
back and just even to say hey there's a
book called the great controversy that
literally lays out you don't even have
to read the whole book go read the last
10 chapters of the book I know I'm stuck
on Mariah but Mariah have you read the
great controversy I'm just curious Yeah.
I'm just curious just to tell people, go
read the last 10 ch 10 10 chapters of
that book and compare it with what you
see happening today. Do you know how
many people would be like, "Yo, Ellen
White's a prophet. I don't care what
else you said about I don't care what
she's a prophet. There is no way that
this woman could have been writing in in
the 1880s writing about what was coming
to happen. And now we're seeing it
happen just as it was said.
But here we are. Here we are being
silent being silent.
So again, when we're looking at all of
these things, as we combine all these
things together and begin to
understand, I think the bottom
line is that I as a
church, we need to be about our father's
business.
We need to be with a united voice.
focused on this thing right here, not
not these other things that you
know tend to divide us. That's
beautiful. Mariah, I'm sorry. I'm so
sorry. No, no, no. Go ahead. She's
saying no, she has not read it, but she
says, "I do believe in Ellen White and
indeed is a prophetist of God." Yes. Uh,
praise God. Mariah, pick up The Great
Controversy. You will be blessed. If you
can, I think you can even read it
online. You could read it online. uh
read those last 10 chapters. Yeah. Um
it's amazing. It's it's amazing to see
um
how how accurate
that book is regarding what is coming
and what is happening right now in our
world. So again to me this is God trying
to wake us up right? Mhm.
There is no even the people out there
who are lifting a warning against this
this what they see as a coming church
state threat. They don't even understand
the significance. They think they
do, but they don't understand where this
is
going. The only people on the face of
the planet that understand where this is
going. You all praise God. Mariah, she
said, "I'm sorry. I'm so stuck on
Mariah." You and Mariah having a whole
conversation conversation because she
said she will um she will be proclaiming
this on her YouTube channel. She says,
"I will proclaim you go." See, that's
just
wow. Yes. Wow. Wow. Mariah or put it or
I can't put the chat. Somebody put it in
the chat. My email so Mariah can can
email us. We want to connect. But
attante at living mana.urch if one of
the producers
um can do that. Atante atlivana.urch and
then we'll continue our discussion
offline. But that's cool. Mariah
definitely want to talk to you. Yeah.
So, what I'm saying is the only voice on
the planet right now that can actually
make
total
sense
of what is happening right now that can
bring this all together. The one voice
is is the Adventist church. Right. So,
my email is Okay, good. They edited it
in the chat. Yeah. Okay. Yeah. That one
voice is the church and
where's our voice? Right. You know what
I'm saying? Where are
we? Uh it it's it's just it's
mindblowing how how
silent we are and yet loud about other
things but silent about this. So I
believe that we're in that time, right?
I believe that we're in that time that
that our voice must be heard, right? We
we have to unite
put our focus on getting this gospel
into all the world. These things are
unfolding before our eyes and God just
keeps giving us, you know, like like who
makes a golden statue,
a big golden statue of it. It's just
it's it's almost funny
in a sense how man is God just giving us
these signs just so obvious
signs because
we're because we're sleeping. It's like
how obvious do I have to make this for
you?
And I think he's making it pretty
obvious. I think he's making it pretty
obvious. Oh, he is making it very
obvious. Yeah. With that said, we're I
think we're going to
There's lots of Man, time has flown.
What time? But we we still have a few
more minutes. Yeah. Well, I'll just
answer any questions because we This was
a question and answer, guys. We kind of
flipped it out. Well, I did answer two
questions, so I did my part. Yeah. And
you're answering questions there.
Everybody else I I'm talking to Mariah,
but so is everybody else. I don't know
if they've heard anything you said.
Everybody's talking to Mariah in the
which is fine. Like Living Mana, like
love on Mariah. That's great. And uh I
think they've already found her YouTube
channel and Yeah. They're they're going
to town. Yeah. Which is cool. Um
Yeah. Okay. I'm curious. I know we were
going to talk offline, but I'm curious
how what Mariah, give us a brief
description of what led you here. Yeah.
While we're still talking, you can put
it in the chat. Yeah. um
a brief description and I think this
movement that we see taking place, I
even saw something in in because we're
here in Huntsville and uh the whole
thing about the Ten Commandments being
in our public school systems. Some
articles came up about that just a few
days ago and for our local for our local
for here in here in Alabama here in
Alabama. And um it's not that
surprising. Yeah, it's not that
surprising because didn't Al Roy Moore
was from Alabama. Roy Moore, that whole
thing back then, but he didn't there
wasn't that kind of momentum. Yeah, he
didn't have the momentum. And and so now
you got, you know, Paula White who is,
you know, she's part of the N the the
the the uh N movement, the whole pro
we're prophets and we we've seen this
and you know, God is going to bring a
mighty w from different countries. Yeah.
angels from the different countries and
all the you got this
merger that is becoming harder and
harder to deny, right? And you know when
I think when people say, "Oh, well, you
never know this could happen. This could
come from, you know, from the atheists
or the Marxists or the unbelievers or
the communists." You got to understand,
and this is what I'm going to be
preaching. I got preaching about today.
Again, when this delusion hits, there
will be no atheists, there will be no
communists, there will be no Marxists.
Everybody is going to be converted after
this new
order.
And
worship will only come from those
professing Christianity, right? So that
means that everyone who's going to be
caught up in this would have been
converted
to this fake or false version of
Christianity. Right. Right. This is not
atheists coming together and saying,
"Hey, you know what? For the sake of the
planet, let's all right." No. No. Far
from it. Far from it. Do you want to
hear what Mariah just Go ahead. She
wrote God gave her a
dream. God gave her a dream. Her dream
was, and this is I'm quoting her. She
said, "I used to be a Trumpup supporting
Christian and then God gave me a dream
that Trump pushed a woman off a tower.
The Holy Spirit revealed to me that
woman was the church."
Wow. Yeah. Wow.
Wow. Definitely take my email down,
Mariah. We We want to contact you. We
want to talk to you.
And I'm not, you know, I don't know. I
can say this
then. So, this is not me saying that,
you know, this this this uh
administration is going to be the one.
But what I am saying, right? I'm just
God how I'm just quoting what she wrote.
how God led her just to lead her to
probably study deeper and just to come
to see that what we're teaching is
truth. And we're not teaching that this
administration. We're just teaching
necessary it's going to be. It could be.
It could be. Yeah. We don't know. But
certainly the things that are being set
up now are being set in place to push
that woman off the ledge. Mhm. And um if
I can just show you this, Mariah,
Revelation 12:17,
the dragon was wroth with the woman,
right? And went to make war with the
remnant of her seed, which keep the
commandments of God and have the
testimony of Jesus, right?
This the dragon the the Bible literally
says that the dragon is going to
attempt to destroy the woman. Yes. And
that woman is the church. Yes.
Mary Anne, our prayer team is gonna pray
for you. They see your prayer request in
the chat.
Yeah.
Yes. Yeah. Well, as soon as I read it,
that's what I thought about. But yeah,
but I guess the Holy Spirit may have
shown her that and I don't know if she
That's amazing. Yeah, that is amazing.
That's amazing.
Um, okay. So, you guys, um, I think
we're gonna we're gonna go ahead and
wrap this up now. Yeah, that went by
really fast.
Remember the sermon today's evangelism
Sabbath sermon. I shared this earlier.
Let me share it again. I'm going to be
speaking on the overmastering delusion
that is going to unite the whole world.
And the reason why this this message is
going to be uh different is
because with this message I've presented
it before, but I've presented it using
quotes from the spirit of prophecy and
the Bible. This message will be strictly
from the Bible. If people are unsure on
how to teach us from the Bible and
you've never heard this from the Bible
alone, this sermon, if you're an
evangelist, if you're doing evangelistic
series and you want to begin to
implement this aspect, which is the most
major aspect. I just can't understand
how how we have missed including this in
our we focus on the papacy. We focus
even on apostate Protestantism but we do
not we talk about spiritualism but we
don't talk about the ultimate act the
final yes spiritualistic stuff is
happening now but we don't talk about
that final thing that brings the whole
world together so we're going to see
that from the Bible and um again invite
your people those who may not be
familiar with this message um this today
is for them today is for them I haven't
heard your sermon but I mean it just
antichrist. Like if he's the antichrist,
they I think people some people just
always thought like, oh, he's just going
to be
I don't know. Like you have to be acting
like you're the real thing. You're not
going to come back like you're just
trying to pretend to be him. Like you're
going to come back like, "No, I'm him."
Yeah. Yeah. That only makes sense. Yeah.
So from the Bible. So remember
this.
Uh let me see. Let me see. Somebody's
saying what time. Like we're you're in
church now. So you this is this is we're
ending our first
service and uh there's a So just keep
watching and you're going to go right
into divine worship and you're not going
to miss the sermon. Yep. And we have
some membership transfers um after we
pray. Okay. And just remember this, you
know, because some people are or at
least I saw one person in the chat
saying that someone that there are those
who have a different view of uh of the
appearing of Satan. And listen, the
bottom line is you got to study to show
yourself approved. And we did do that
together. Yeah. We did a series on
Matthew 24, right? I was like I was like
I think I Matthew it's called 24. Okay.
We went through the entire we did like I
don't know 10 presentations just on
Matthew 24 before the test and the Yeah.
Is it before? Yeah. Does Satan appear on
the test or after the test is done? Um
so there are people that believe
differently and you know this is no it's
not like well you're lost if you believe
this particular thing differently right?
You're Adventist and you think this way
versus this way. But you got to be
convicted in your own mind. Not, well,
this pastor said this, this pastor said
that, which one should I believe? I like
both of these pastors, or this is my
favorite pastor. No, you cannot judge
based off of You got to judge based off
of your conviction on the word of God.
Yeah. Okay. Definitely. So, I will end
it there. All right. We're going to pray
and then we have uh first reading. Yeah,
first reading. All right. Heavenly
Father, please uh just bless us, Lord.
Um thank you Lord for giving us this
time to to talk about current events and
where we are um in earth's history. Lord
help us to be uh committed Lord to your
word. Um help us Lord to raise our
voices on what is happening in our world
in this country today. Lord please help
us to speak with conviction. Help us to
speak the truth. Help us Lord. help us
forgive us for our silence and Lord um
please just put within us the spirit um
of courage the spirit of truth Lord that
we may be about your business. Thank you
Lord for hearing and answering. We pray
this in Jesus name. Amen. Amen. Amen.
All right. Well, we are excited to do a
first reading of a membership transfer.
Just want to let you guys know that if
you want to become a member of Living
Mana Church, there's three ways you can
do it. I talk a little bit more about
this um in the service as well, but uh
you this is the email that you're going
to use for all three of those ways. So,
if you want to become a member, you need
to write down that email that you see,
patrice livinga.live.
uh because you can if you're a 7th Day
Adventist, you can trans if you're a
member of another church in good
standing, you can transfer your
membership and you're going to use that
email that's there on your screen. If
you are a baptized Christian and you
want to join the 7th Day Adventist
Church, but you don't feel like you have
to get rebaptized, then you can email
Patrice there at living.live.
And if you want to get baptized um and
you have studied uh what Adventist uh
would believe from the Bible and you
want to become a member, you can get
baptized, I like to say, and Pastor
Myers will actually come out and baptize
you. So, uh if that's what you would
like, you can email Patrice
living.live, but we have a membership
transfer
and let's see here. And then
um let's see. All right. So we have the
first reading for Olivia Torres from
Edenburgg 7day Adventist Church. And so
I'm not sure where Edenberg is. I don't
know what state. But we are happy that
Olivia wants to become a member of the
Living Mana Church. So we're excited
about that. and there will be a second
reading and then you will become an
official member and we will we will
welcome you. Amen. All right. So, um so
I'm going to share something. No, I'm
not going to share it. All right. We're
just going to wait. We're just going to
wait. We're just going to wait. All
right. We'll continue to worship with
us. Don't go anywhere. You don't want to
miss that sermon that's coming up. Um
and our prayer time that we have in the
divine service with the Sowells and the
good music that we have prepared for you
as well. So stay tuned. and we'll see
you in the divine worship service.
[Music]
Amen.
There feeling that I don't
belong. The comforts of this world is
blinded me to the rest that I deserve.
But even in my blindness, my spirit
reaches
out. There has to be much more to life.
Here on the east side of Aahu, about a
third of a mile off the shores of Koul
Beach, we found a very famous island
called Moiki, most commonly known as
China man's hat. I lived in Hoy all my
life, but I've never taken the time to
explore this tiny island. So, I'm stoked
to be able to do it today. You see, one
of my favorite sayings in life is this.
Blessed are the curious, for they shall
always have adventures. And blessed are
the adventurous, for they shall always
have great pictures to show and awesome
stories to tell. You see, my friends,
this life is full of awesome discoveries
and new adventures every single day. But
in order to find them, we got to be
willing to get off the couch, get out of
the house, and start living our lives in
the real world instead of the artificial
world of Hollywood movies and social
media. One person said it like this. You
can't discover new oceans unless you're
willing to lose sight of the shore. And
that, my friends, is the truth. Those
who choose to spend their lives on the
shores of complacency and comfort often
miss out on the oceans of adventure and
the islands of experience. So, it's
either you launch out or you miss out.
And for me, I don't want to miss out on
anything. So, today we're going to
explore more as we launch out to see
what's happening on China.
Take me
home. Take me home. Now, this island
obviously got its nickname due to its
likeness to the rice hats of Asia. Now,
these Asian rice hats are not the most
fashionable, but they're definitely
practical. And in my opinion, practical
is more important than fashionable,
especially on a hot Hawaiian day like
today. You see, the conical shape of
these hats is such that it provides a
nice shade from the sun and even a small
shelter from the rains. In the rice
fields of Asia, it protects the farmers
from getting toasted from the powerful
rays of the sun. But these hats are not
only helpful in Asia. I'm finding it
very useful on a hot summer day like
today.
[Music]
As beautiful as it is, this island just
doesn't have much when it comes to
shade. A bunch of bushes, few coconut
trees here and there. It's just like the
top of an Asian rice hat. It absorbs all
the heat of the afternoon sun.
Jesus is the answer I'm found beyond
myself. And now I know that all my hope
is found in him and nothing else. You
see, just as my Asian rice hat has
provided shade from the hot Hawaiian
sun, so too does our God cover us from
the sun of trial in the heat of
hardship. The Bible says that the Lord
is your keeper and your shade on your
right hand. The sun shall not strike you
by day, nor the moon by night. The Lord
will keep you from all evil. He will
keep your life. For he has been a
stronghold to the poor and to the needy,
a shelter from the storm, and a shade
from the heat. Now, God doesn't stop the
son of trial from shining. He did
promise that life would always be cool
and refreshing and easy. But he did
promise to preserve us in pain, to cover
us in conflict, and to shield us in
sorrow. He has pledged to us his holy
word that when things begin to heat up
in our lives, that he is our shade by
day, our defense by night, and a shelter
in the time of storm. And as long as we
remain under his covering, we will be
able to rise above the heat of this
world and stand at the top of the
mountain of victory. We will then trade
our China's hats for a royal diadem, a
crown of everlasting life. And then we
will rise from this earthly paradise to
the sweet paradise of
God. Take me
home. Take me
home. Heat.
Heat.
[Music]
Heat. Heat. Heat.
N. Heat. Heat.
[Music]
Heat. Heat.
Heat.
[Music]
Heat. Heat.
Heat. Heat. Heat.
[Music]
Welcome back, Living Mana Church family.
We're so happy that you decided to stay
with us today on this Sabbath and
worship, continue to worship with us. It
is so good to see all of you here. If
you're just joining us today, just now
you weren't dur you weren't here for our
first program, please put in the chat
where you are watching from. We want to
say a special welcome to you. If this is
your very first time visiting, please
put a one in the chat so we can say an
even even more extra special welcome to
you. And so we are just happy that you
are here and worshiping with us today.
Um, I have to say that earlier program
was was really really good and it was it
was being completely worked out by the
Holy Spirit um, as far as how it went
exactly. Uh, because we had different
plans. We were just going to do regular
question and answer and we did get some
questions and I was able to answer some
of the mental health but God took it
another direction and it really was a
blessing. So again, put in the chat
where you're viewing from. Just want to
say a welcome to you. I see uh, Lubox,
Texas. Welcome. I see a one, but I don't
see the name. So, um, let's see if I can
see that. Oh, got a few ones. Okay, so
we have Rolando, uh, Pence, welcome.
Good to see you here. Tom, uh, Fra, good
to see you here as well. This is your
first time. Oh, we have another one.
Priscilla from New Mexico, welcome to
Living Mana Church. And to all of you
who are just joining us for the first
time, just to want you to know that this
is a
100% online 7th Day Adventist Church.
It's the first official online 7th Day
Adventist Church. We're with the
Northeastern Conference. And so we have
programming not just I keep seeing okay
as the ones are coming up, we have more
ones. Barbara Edwards, welcome. Um but I
just want you to know again we have
programming all throughout the week. We
are not just here on Sabbath. We have
mental health programs on Monday and
that is led by by myself. I'm a licensed
marriage and family therapist and Dr.
Ricardo White is my co-host and he is a
psychiatrist. We have True Health
Tuesdays. On Tuesday we have two doctors
um one licensed naturopathic doctor uh
an MD and we have a licensed uh
nutritionist as well. And so they are
bringing uh the programs to you on
Tuesday and giving you so much great
information about your health and what
you can do to make your health better.
And then we have our prayer team that
leads out in our power Wednesdays uh
every Wednesday. And I can tell you that
it's called Power Wednesday and it is
very powerful. So you won't want to miss
that or you might want to check it out.
And then Thursdays, our young adult uh
youth pastor um he has a program on
Thursdays as well. And so these are
programs you're not going to want to
miss. And we have a great way to remind
you. And I'm going to tell you how to do
that here just shortly. Looks like we
had more ones than people telling us
where they're Oh, no. We got some people
from Madagascar. All right. Madagascar,
welcome here to Living Mata Church. um
from Collegedale, not too far away. Hope
you're staying dry. I'm just assuming
you're probably getting the rain, too,
because you're just in Collegeell,
Tennessee. Um and Barbara, again, I
welcomed you, but you're watching from
Mississippi. That's great. Michelle from
Portland, Oregon. Good to see you.
Michelle, always good to see you here.
Barbara from Anguila, always good to see
you here. And then we have Melanie from
Paris, France. Welcome, Melanie. Good to
have you here uh from Paris and yeah
looks like we have quite the
international group today but we are an
international church and so we are just
happy to have each and every one of you
and I want to let all of you know how
you can stay connected to living mana
church and for the ones those who are
visiting for the first time pay very
close attention to this um because this
is how you're going to stay connected to
living mana church and be reminded of
all the things that I just mentioned
that we do um and so you will get
notifications when we go live for these
different programs um that we are doing.
So I want to tell you on how you can
sign up to get text alert alerts if
you're here in America and you can do
that by texting LMOC to
855207-4107. You can see it there on
your screen. You can also scan the QR
code. And again, that only works if you
are here in the United States. If you
are out of the country, which many of
you are, um you need to sign up for
Mighty Networks and you can see the link
in our chat. And Mighty Networks is our
virtual home. Like I said, um we we are
100% online church, but we do have a
virtual church home and it is mighty
networks and that is where you will be
able to get reminders and announcements.
You will also be able to learn about all
our different small groups and th those
who are just visiting I want you to
check mighty networks out um because
there we have different small groups
that you might be interested in joining
and this is where we form community here
at Living Managed Church because you are
able to get to know people um and get to
you know contact the leaders and become
friends with the other people in the
group and it's just it's again this is
where we form community. It's a lot of
fun and hopefully you choose a small
group that um is something that you're
interested in so that you will really
love and be passionate about being a
part of that group if that's what you're
wanting to do. So, just wanted to let
you all know how you can be um just all
caught up with everything Living Man
Church is doing. That's by getting text
alerts and also signing up for mighty
networks. So, you can get all that
information there as well. Also just
want to remind you guys and for our
first timers let you know that we do
have LOC kids at LOC kids meets at 11:30
central time on Sabbath morning. It goes
for about an hour and a half. And if you
want more information about your kids
getting signed up for LOCC kids, you can
text kids to that 855 number that you
see on your screen or you can email and
the leadership there will get back to
you about how your kids can get
involved. And so that is
locidana.urch. That's the way that
you're going to get your kids involved
um in
LOLC kids is using that email or texting
kids to that 855 number. Want to remind
you guys that Pastor Myers does have
virtual office hours. But you know
before that let's use that that slide on
the screen. The membership. Okay. We can
go to office hours. We'll do office
hours and then go back to membership. So
Pastor Meyers does have virtual office
hours. If you're needing to speak with
him, please email, schedule an
appointment by emailing patrice
livingmana.live. Don't forget that email
because the membership email is the same
email uh that you will be emailing if
you want to become a member. And I did
talk about that at the end uh or when we
did a train when we did the first
reading for membership after Sabbath
school that there are three ways that
you can become a member. And if you want
to transfer your membership, use that
email there, patrice livinga.live. If
you want to come in by profession of
faith, you can use that email. And if
you want to be baptized, you can use
that email. Um, and that's the way
you're going to uh we're going to be
able to start uh the process for you
being able to join uh Living Mana
Church. So, we are excited for all of
you who are those who are wanting to be
a part of Living Mana Church. We welcome
you and are excited for you to come and
be a part of this mission here at this
church. Also just want to remind you
guys that prayer requests I talked to
you about our prayer team and our prayer
team is u just willing and can't wait
for you to send in your prayer request
so that they can pray for you. And if
you want them to do that you can email
them pray living
manana.urch and you can send your
request in that way. Like I was
mentioning Mighty Networks, there's a
prayer wall on Mighty Network. So you if
you um sign up for Mighty Networks, you
can put your prayer request on the
prayer wall and the prayer team takes
those prayer requests from the prayer
wall and puts it into their system so
that they can pray or you can text pray
to that 855 number and the prayer team
will get it and they will pray over your
request. And so there's many different
ways to get your prayer request in, but
I can tell you that the prayer team uh
they really enjoy doing this and they
are passionate about it and they love
praying for you and your prayer request.
You are not alone. You are not alone.
Okay. want you guys to also know that if
you are watching on Power of the Lamb uh
YouTube page, we want you to jump over
to my Living Mana YouTube page and we
want you to like and subscribe there as
well. We're trying to grow our uh Living
Mana YouTube page and if you would do
that for us, that helps us out a lot.
Once you guys Well, I want you to put a
one in the chat. How many of you were
there live or have watched the uh the
broad the replay broadcast for True
Health Tuesday this last Tuesday with
Dr. Maria Humel? Did you watch that?
Because I was able to watch a little bit
of that and it was so good. Put a one in
the chat. I mean her numbers were she
had a large audience. I know some of you
were there. Um definitely and it was
such a blessing. Um, and so I just want
to let you guys know that Maria is doing
it every other week, so she won't be
here this week, but I know she gave you
a challenge and a lot of resources for
you to do within that time. Um, and so
please, you're going to want to follow
up with that, but just wanted everyone
to know that she will be back in two
weeks. So, not this Tuesday, but the
following Tuesday. And um, there I see
the ones coming up. And it was really a
blessing. We're so blessed to have her
uh be a part of the True Health Tuesday
team, but also she is a member of Living
Mana Church and see we are just so
blessed to have her here with
us. Want you also to know that
Afterglow, so many of you love
Afterglow. I know I love Afterglow and
it has been on Altar Live for the first
three years of living mana's existence.
It has been uh on Altar Live. Ultralive
is having some issues, some um if if
you're on a phone, it will, you know, do
some glitches and not allow you to do
all the things to enjoy the experience
on Ultra Live. When you're on a
computer, it definitely does better and
doesn't seem to do the things that it
does on a phone. But a lot of our
viewers watch some of these programs on
their phone because it's right in their
hand. So with that said, after Glow will
be meeting in two or moving I should say
in two weeks it's going to officially
move to Mighty Networks and so we will
be giving you more information about
that. Also
um Pastor Myers is planning uh some new
events and things like that and you have
some of you have been uh messaged in uh
Mighty Network. So please check your
mighty network me mighty network
messages and please respond to that
message. So we are just um excited about
to continue to grow our afterglow uh
after the sermon. It really is a
blessing to see everybody's perspective
and what they got from the sermons and
Sabbath school. Just want to remind you
guys that we do have an adult Sabbath
school uh study that studies the
quarterly every Friday evening from 6:30
to 8:00 p.m. Central and that is led out
from gems and that's that is the acronym
for golden aers emerging into mature
saint saints and they are a great group
of people. So if you are wanting to to
study the uh quarterly the adult Sabbath
school lesson that the whole world 7th
day a church studies then definitely you
want to join the gym's adult Sabbath
school class that is every Friday um at
6:30 to 8:00 p.m. you can participate
there with them. Also just want to
remind you about STAR our steps to
addiction recovery. And so that's
Thursdays at 7 central time on Alter
Live currently. And so you will be able
to contact if you're wanting more
information about the steps to addiction
recovery. You can connect with Gina
Brower on Mighty Networks to get more
information um about that
program. Want to remind you guys that we
we are already going around the world as
you can see. We have so many viewership
from around the world. But we also want
to uh make our living mana global page
um impact the world with the languages
of the world. And as you know there's
seven seven different languages that
Pastor Meyer's sermons can be translated
into. Um for those who have not seen
this, just want to give you again
another idea so that you can start just
familiarize yourself with this uh
YouTube page that and if you know people
who speak Chinese, Spanish, French, um
can't think of all of them right off. I
know Ukrainian I can't think of all the
names right now. Those are just some.
But you can go through the list and see
uh what we have. If you know anyone that
speaks those languages and you think it
would be better for them to hear the
sermon in their language because that's
how they can understand it better,
definitely share. But I want to give you
uh just a little uh sample of what that
looks like.
Isn't that cool? We think that's amazing
that that technology is out there and um
we are able to utilize um this
technology and so continue to pray over
LMLC Global and you can also support
LMLC Global um because we have to
repurchase this package every year. And
so if you would like to continue to
support um Living Mana Church uh LMLC
Global going into all of the world and
the languages of the world uh you could
put that on your tithe envelope and and
we have an editor that's dedicated to
that um um who is able to um or has to
translate the slides and everything into
those languages. So that is the the
whole package. Um but again you can
support through your prayers and through
your financial gifts and you can mark
that on your tithes as well. Speaking of
tithe and offering, it is that time uh
to let you know how you can give to
continue to help support Living Mana
Church or start supporting Living Mana
Church for the first time. First of all,
as I always say, thank you for just
being a huge blessing to this church for
three years. We have been here for three
years and God has led us all the way.
And it's because of again your
faithfulness and because of God putting
it upon your heart and you obeying what
God is putting on your heart. So again,
thank you for supporting the church. But
if you would like to continue to support
the church and if or start to support
the church, you can virtually be able to
give to uh to Living Mana Church by
going to adventistgiving.org.
you will click in the right um hand
corner and you will see a tithe envelope
and there you can see where you can give
your tithe uh which supports the north
uh eastern conference and the worldwide
church of 7-day adventism and then
there's a place where you can give to
the local church which helps us to do
the things that we do here for living
manage church there's also an area there
on your tithe envelope where you can
give to the benevolence fund which helps
people who are um in need. There's also
a education fund that um helps uh young
people that might just need a little bit
of extra funds to um for their their
Christian education. Um and you got to
see two of them last week who were
looking for some assistance and they're
getting ready to graduate in biology,
premed, and become doctors. And so, um
and they're, you know, just great
Christian young ladies. But there's
other students out there who are just,
you know, needing just a little bit of
assistance. And so there's an education
fund that you can give to and there's
many other things on your tithe
envelope. So please go check that out.
If you do not want to give virtually,
you can mail in a check to uh Living
Mana Church. There's the address on the
screen. It's P Box 428, Owens
Crossroads, Alabama
35763. and you can give that way to help
support the church in all the different
things that the church does. And again,
we just praise God. We praise God that
here it is the first Sabbath in the
month of May and we are three years old
because our our our celebration was in
April, right? Our first sab Sabbath,
excuse me, was April 9th um three years
ago. And so here we are. We are three
years and one month old. So we every
we're thankful every I don't know this
church to be honest this is the first
time you know I thought about the other
day I was like this was really a church
plant and my husband and I we had never
planted a church just from scratch you
know there are other pastors who had
planted churches but we were not a part
of that and hadn't done that but I was
like this is a church plant it's online
but it's still a church plant so to see
something grow from nothing to what
Living Man Church is now it really is a
blessing and It's a witness to us and
it's a it's an encouragement to us of
what God can do and it builds our faith.
So hopefully it builds yours too. But we
are just so thankful for all of you for
what you do for Living Mana Church.
There's so many volunteers on on the
team that help support uh this church. I
was just this morning I heard my husband
speaking to his his graphic or his slide
team. Um what they do like when he
preaches sermons like don't think pastor
puts those together because he does not.
There is a whole graphics and slide team
that does that. They're amazing. Every
group of of um in in this church is
amazing. Um the the our broadcast team I
I should not start listing because
that's g not going to be good because
there's so many. But our I always talk
about our prayer team, but there's just
so many different uh groups of people
that are such a blessing. We couldn't do
this without without you guys. Like we
can't do this by ourselves by no means.
like we just couldn't do it. So, it's
God, you and God is using us as well.
And so, we are thankful. And it's you
out there. It's you out there. You make
this happen as well. You definitely make
this happen. You show up, you tell your
friends, you share the videos. And so,
it's it's everybody all hands on deck to
make this happen. And so, we are just
very thankful. So, I just want to give a
praise, a prayer of praise and
thanksgiving to God at this time. If you
would please just bow your heads with me
as we pray.
Heavenly Father, Lord, just want to
thank you for this Sabbath and the rest
that Sabbath brings, Lord. No work, no
bill paying, no school, none of that. We
can just worship you today. That's it.
And that's such a blessing, Lord. It's
not that's it. That's like the biggest
blessing in life to just be able to
worship you. I thank you for the Sabbath
and what it brings, Lord. It's just
peace and rest. And Lord, I just want to
lift up those who um are hurting right
now. Lord, there's so many people out
there that are they're here. They're
showing up for church. They're showing
up to worship you, but they're hurting.
And I'm asking that you will bless them.
That you will bless them um in their
marriage. You will bless them if they
are single in their life and the things
that they are needing. That you will uh
bless them if they are ill and sick.
Lord, give them peace. Heal them. show
them what to do, how to help take care
of their body. Lead them to the right
doctors, Lord. Just bless them, Lord.
And for all those parents that are
praying for their children, Lord, help
them to just trust you because you love
those kids more than they do. And so,
you are doing everything in your power
to save them. And so, parents, keep
praying, but we can relax. We can
believe in what you are doing in our
children's lives. Lord, again, I thank
you for Living Mana Church and the
blessing all of the viewing audience and
membership is to this church and to us
personally. And Lord, I just pray that
you will be with Pastor Meyers that this
is a he's never preached anything like
what he's about to preach today. And so,
I'm excited and I know everyone else,
they should be excited, but I just pray
that you will um give him an outpouring
of your Holy Spirit uh that he will be
able to share this and it will be so
impactful in all of our lives in Jesus
name.
[Music]
[Applause]
Amen.
[Music]
Heat. Heat. Heat.
What's up everybody? We're Brotherhood
Music. Massive shout out to Elevate
Studios for having us here to j out this
song called Open Week Eyes. We pray and
hope that it blesses you guys out there
as much as it blesses us.
[Music]
Open the eyes of my heart,
Lord. Open the eyes of my
heart. I want to
see you.
I want to see
[Music]
you. Open the eyes of my heart,
Lord. Open the eyes of my
heart. I want to see
you. I want to
see you.
to see you high
lifted
[Music]
up. Shining in the light of your
glory. Pour out your power and
love as we sing. Holy,
holy,
holy to see you. I lift it
up, shining in the light of your
glory. Pour out your power and
love as we sing holy, holy, holy.
I want to
see
you. I want to
[Music]
you. Open the eyes of my heart,
Lord. Open the eyes of my
heart. I want to see.
I want to see
[Music]
you. Open the eyes of my heart,
Lord. Just open the eyes of my
heart. I want to
see you.
I want to
see you. Oh, to see you high and lift it
up.
Yeah. Shining in the light of your
glory. Pour out, pour out your power and
love as we sing. Holy,
holy, holy to see you high and lift it
up. Oh
hol, shining in the light of your
glory. Pour out, pour out your power and
love as we sing. Holy,
holy, holy,
holy,
holy. I want to
see
you. I want to
see you.
[Music]
I want to
see
you. Here at Living Mana, we bear each
other's burdens. When you need support
or prayer, when you're feeling
discouraged or alone or
anxious, you don't have to face life
struggles alone.
[Music]
Let us come boldly unto the throne of
grace that we may obtain mercy and find
grace to help in our time of
need. The Lord is close to the
brokenhearted and saves those who are
crushed in spirit.
[Music]
Amen. Greetings saints of the most high
God and welcome to another edition of
Living Mana's prayer and praise time.
Hallelujah saints as always. I'm here
with my lovely Brian Amra you know and
she was just telling me this morning you
know what since we kind of started with
the new studio. She's like I don't feel
like we're so close
anymore. She feels like she's way over
there. I don't know. I'm just used to
shouldertoshoulder I guess. Well, uh,
well, prayer brings us together, doesn't
it, saints? Bring prayer brings us
together. And listen, um, again, I
wanted to thank the Living Man of Tech
team one more time, Brother Josh,
Brother Colin, Brother Gavin, and our
beloved Sister Patrice, who we gave a
shout out to last week, but she wasn't
in the studio, but she's in the studio
live this week at the top of the roll
call. Sister Patrice, we love you. Thank
God for you. so precious to us and uh
looking forward to seeing you and
chopping it up with you. And again,
saints, a few more shout
outs. Yeah. Uh there was somebody I
wanted to Oh, this you know what
blessing says to scoot over.
Okay. Okay. We got
Okay. So, so look, um this morning I had
opportunity to to chat with Sister
Charlotte really quickly and I see you
there in the chat. Sister Charlotte
doing your thing. Sister Charlotte is
one of our newest prayer warriors. Y'all
already know she's family member. She's
living in a family, but she is now
official uh LMOC war. And so we're thank
God for her. We are also thanking God
for Sister Denise Richardson who is a
ball of fire, a blessing to us. Sister
Sharon Fay, our Loc news correspondent
on the scene with the good news. Amen.
And Sharon gave an amazing testimony on
Power Wednesday last week. Look at here.
You all should have heard that
testimony. Actually, we have it
recorded, but uh what a testimony she
gave about staying on the boat, staying
in the in in on on the ship of Z. She
welcome back home. It was I think it was
in it was the theme was hope. Beautiful
stuff, Sister Sharon. We're glad to have
you on the team. Also, Sister Stacy
Ferguson is our one of our newest
special ops prayer warriors. So, welcome
to them. Welcome to the new prayer
warriors. God is sending us all the help
we need. And as first lady said, you
know, all of these ministries and teams
you see, you see Amber and I sit here.
But look, we're held up by one of the
most
amazing group of servants and prayer
warriors and warriors and they do a
great work behind the scenes. Sister
Angela who we love bombed this week, you
know, with a surprise love appreciation
party we had for her. God has sent help
now to fortify her. She was doing so
much of the she was the the
administrative arm of the prayer
ministry, but now God has sent some
beautiful help to her. Her and sister
Ayana now have some uh lovely sisters
who will be there helping them. So, a
lot of the administrative work now, you
know, takes some pressure off of her
shoulders and uh we thank God for it.
and also our special ops team is going
to start growing and bursting at the
seams especially when we begin to
implement some of the plans that pastor
have and some of the vision he has to
grow the prayer team and to grow the
body of Christ here at Living Mana. So
with all of that, thank y'all saints.
Thank you for your prayers. And it's not
just the prayer warriors. The members of
this church are praying. I'm looking in
this chat this morning and I'm seeing
brother Kashif standing strong in the
gap. Sister Miracella, Sister Ayana,
Sister uh Blessing, and all of you in
the chat. Thank you so much. Living men
of prayer warriors, Elder Plant, I see
him. He's standing up there, too.
Everybody just circling the wagons uh
and and loving on one another the way
Jesus would have us do it. We thank God
for it. Um, one other thing I wanted to
make sure we say special prayers for our
beloved brother Danny and sister Jackal
and Clark. They're on vacation enjoying
some good uh RNR. Much deserved
vacation. They do so much for this
church. Absolutely. Y'all know they do
the Revelation Bible study. Jackie is
cooking up something healthy and good in
the kitchen and every week. And they're
on special ops teams. They are prayer
leaders. They are facilitators and hosts
for Power Wednesday. I mean, just on and
on and on. What a blessing they are ever
since they've been here. So, we are
thankful for them. And we're I was
chatting with Jackie a little bit this
morning that we're they're they're
wanting to get some supernatural uh uh
refreshing from the Lord. So, lift them
up in prayer, saints. Amen. Amen. Amen.
Um uh we're seeing your prayer request
in the chat. Sister Teresa had God bless
you. We will continue to pray for you
and the Hatton family. I saw you there.
I saw you this week at at uh mental
health Monday. You were right there
enjoying it right along with us and want
to encourage all y'all come on out
saints and be blessed throughout the
week as first lady has announced. Sister
Sakara, love you so much. See you there.
Sister Emma Jean, I shout it out to you
this morning. AR, enough love go around
for everybody. Thank you for your prayer
request. We'll read some of that off in
just a moment. But um I believe that's
just about it for today. Oh, I want you
know what? First lady's
t-shirt that stuck with me. Seek first.
Uh in the huddle this morning, Sister
Shaunie was teaching us about uh
praising the Lord first and and not
focusing on the negativity. That's what
the enemy is trying to do. get us to
focus on all that negativity, but you
know, it takes some discipline and some
practice, but learn to seek him first
and learn to turn to him first before we
respond, before we react. I like that.
It's a good reminder for me. That is a
great reminder for everybody.
Amen. It's so true. You know, I have to
capture my thoughts and give them to the
Lord all the time. Amen. That's all of
us, sweetheart. And uh you know I was
telling the the the prayer warriors in
the huddle uh you were looking at me you
really are looking at a miracle saints
because one time all I knew was
negativity and darkness and and a bunch
of chains and a bunch of uh habits and
addictions and things that I use to cope
with life. And when I decided I want
when the Lord touched my heart and woke
me up from the sleep of death and and
and let me know I needed Jesus and that
he was there for me. I realized I didn't
have any strength within and of myself
to get over these habits and addictions
and way of life. So God be to transform
and renew my mind. You hear the pastor
talking about neuroplasticity. God has
fearfully and wonderfully created us
that we can be transformed and we can be
changed. But we got to cooperate with
him. So I'm really thankful for the
change and the miracle change in my own
life. He did it for me saints. He can do
it for you. So, sweetheart, what what
what are we reporting to today about God
and his goodness and all he's been doing
in the lives of the people? All right.
Well, we see all of your greetings in
the chat. First off, we're just going to
do uh, you know, all round roll call.
So, thank you so much everyone for your
kind messages to us. And Eddie, I see
you there. God bless you. Oh, you said
we're gonna we're gonna do an all all
around. Okay, so we're so many. He's
telling me don't get specific, but hey
everybody. Hey Nicole, you know. Uh oh,
here we go. First lady says, "I'm not
going to start calling out these groups
cuz it it's it's so powerful. It pulls
you in." You see why it's going to take
eternity fellowshipping and worshiping
in heaven because it's going to take
forever to love on everybody like this
right here. Don't you want to be there,
saints? Look, I want to be there.
Trevor, you gonna be there, brother? God
can do it. He's able to do it, brother.
Amen. Amen. Hey, Ayana. Okay. Well, I
guess we're kind of doing this verse and
vision. Hello. Hello, Ayanna. Sister
Emily, Nicole,
hallelujah, Barbara, my brother Leon,
Jamie, hallelujah. Amen. Sister Regina,
it's spiritual. I see you there.
Hallelujah. All
right. Hello, everybody. Praying for
you. It's spiritual. We see your message
in the chat. Praying for you, beloved.
Okay. So, before I get into the praise
reports, just a reminder that if you
would like to submit your prayer
requests and praise reports, you can
send an email to pray living
mana.urch. You can also post on the
mighty networks prayer wall. Um, we are
still always looking for people to join
our prayer team and special ops teams.
We have an overflow of people who need
prayer um and who have requested uh
special ops prayer teams to for
themselves or their loved ones. So um if
you would like to join the prayer team,
join a special ops team under the prayer
team umbrella, please send an email to
praymanana.urch. If you need a special
ops team for yourself or a loved one,
please send an email to spec ops. That's
s
pops
livingmana.urch. If you would like to
join the women's ministry on mighty
networks, please send an email to women
livinga.urch. And finally, if you would
like to join the men's ministry, please
send an email to sevenloaves. That's s e
ven l o a ve
livingmana.urch. I believe a lot of that
is going up in the chat. Amen. Amen. All
right. First up from Artell Peters. I
want to thank the prayer team for the
acknowledgement of my request in prayer
to pass my driver's license road exam.
It was the second attempt within two
months that the road test was not made
available for me. I gave praise for what
and why. I do not know the reason, but
God does. And I have comfort in his
knowledge and grace that is sufficient
for me. Artell, I just want to tell you
that I appreciate your attitude of
praise through something that can be
extremely frustrating. So, thank you for
that refreshing praise. Um, Amen. And we
do pray that you will be able to take
your road exam soon. Um, but you are
correct. God knows what, why, and how.
Amen. Amen. From Francis Grant, this is
her original prayer request. Please pray
for Dominique, a 10year-old who had a
terrible fall and he is in a
coma. Update and a praise report. Prayer
warriors update on Dominique. He is not
out of the woods, but he is beginning to
have some responses. To God be the
glory. Please continue to lift him up in
prayer that the Lord may fully restore
him to
health. From Ayanna Tobias praise
report. I got an email from my job
saying that I am no longer acting in the
position that I'm in right now. I got
confirmed in that position. Glory to
God. Praise God. We are so happy for
you. Yes. from Gerald
Best. Thanking God. An elder at my
church in Maryland, Jerome Doo Good was
diagnosed with cancer a few months ago.
This past Sabbath, his daughter came
inside the church where I was standing
and said, "My dad is cancerree. Praise
God." All praises to God and thanks for
the prayers that went up for Elder
Jerome from Annette Rivas. And this is
the final praise report of this
session. Happy Sabbath family. I want to
thank you all for praying over my court
on Thursday. I submitted my answers to
the court and they accepted them. Praise
God. I have court next month to resolve
the case, praying that God may allow the
judge to see the unfairness of the case
and rule in my favor or even better have
the situation resolved without having to
go to court again. May God's will be
done. We will be continuing to pray for
that, Annette. But we praise God that
your answers were accepted. So, Amen.
Come on, somebody. Yeah, we love your
praise for us. Please continue to send
your praise reports in. I truly believe
that it gives people hope, faith,
encouragement, and positivity seeing how
the Lord works through our lives and our
prayers. Yes, it does. And and what
would prayer be without praise? We got
to tell it what God has done. Amen. And
and how good he is. It's not a cliche to
say, you know, he he's a doctor in the
hospital room. He's a lawyer in the
courtroom. A friend that stickketh
closer than a brother, a rock in a weary
land, water when you're thirsty, shelter
in a time of storm. Come on, somebody.
We We love praising God that way because
that's exactly who and what he is.
Hasn't he done something good for you?
Send it in. Let's talk about it, y'all.
Come on. That's right. Praise him. I see
you, saints. See, we got some folk in
here. I already know we got some folk I
I can't wait to meet y'all in when we
have the praise session because see we
got some folk here who who just looking
for an excuse to have a praise party.
Amen. Amen. Amen. We got to give him
praise saints because listen, we are the
church militant and we're about to be up
against a whole lot of stuff in this
world when the whole world's a raid
against us. But guess what? We can't let
them steal our praise, saints. Amen. We
can't let him steal our joy. We got to
keep on praising him anyhow. And so
we're getting ready to go to the to the
throne of grace one more time.
Hallelujah. Sister Anetta Carr, I see
you there. And um you know, we talk
about these prayer warriors. Today we're
going to be uh our special guest is one
of the most beautiful sisters I've ever
met. She's so strong and such a a a a
source of support for this prayer team,
for Pastor Antante, for me and Amra. We
love this sister so much and she's gonna
come. But before she does, I want us
gonna read off a few prayer requests
because she's going to just lead us in
prayer. But I want to mention some of
your prayer requests before we bring my
big sister on. Amen. I see you, brother
Keith. I see you there. That's for a
praise party. Hallelujah. And so Lord,
we we are seeking you for something to
praise about. So listen, I want to just
read off a few of these prayer uh
requests, but I want to remind you after
listening to pastor speak during Sabbath
school. I was reminded of a prayer
request I wrote in the back of one of my
old Bibles from prison. I still have it
here. I just had to cut it out and stick
it in here, but it says, "Father Yahweh,
make me a voice in the earth." Oh. When
I Yeah. When I wrote this in the back of
that Bible, I was in prison. When I
wrote that prayer request in there,
shortly after that, God made me a
seven-day adventist and gave me
something to tell the people about. I
saw you, Brother Rowan. I saw your
prayer request in the chat earlier. You
says, "I'm still not sure of what to
tell them." God will make you a voice.
And that's not just for you, Brother
Johnson. That's for others who are
watching. God will give you something to
tell, a story to tell, a message to
share. He will take what's going on in
your life and relate it personally to
what we're learning in prophecy. This is
the message God has given us. You are
the message. We are the message. Study
to show yourself approved and watch that
word come alive. I love what brother
Kirk put in the men's chat a little
while ago. As we begin to study, we
really want to know the truth. We begin
to study. That thing will just open up
to us. God will open those divine truths
up to us. I don't mean to start
preaching here, but I just want to
encourage you. Let us become a voice and
not be quiet. Let's not be silent. We
don't have to be silent. We don't have
to be silent, church. And so I'm praying
for me, God, revive my voice and for the
7th Day Adventist Church, all
Adventists, all even non-Adventists.
God, give them a word to speak because
uh it won't be long once you start
studying. You will become one. I can
assure you that this is the truth. Also,
we want to pray for uh
um Mary Lynn. She wants to be delivered
from anxiety attacks. Uh, Brother Ronin,
we just mentioned your prayer request.
Sister Jenny Edward is asking us to
remember Dion Sears, who's on a
ventilator in the hospital. Nicole is
asking for prayer for her friend Sonia.
It's an urgent prayer request that just
came in. We don't know the details, but
we know God does. Sister Deborah Hailing
has an unspoken request. We're praying
for you. Sister Katie, God bless you.
Love you. Happy Sabbath. We're praying
for a sister of a family friend, right,
whose husband came in and found her face
down and unconscious. She had a
pulmonary embolism and she's on a
ventilator. So, we're praying for her.
Uh, AR, we saw your message in the chat.
You had a terrible flare up of eczema
and um uh it was a dermatitis skin flare
up that lasted for several weeks. And
you said that you're you're not a member
and you kind of feel guilty about asking
for prayer. Do not never feel guilty.
Our God has enough love to go around and
so we are honored and privileged to be
able to pray for you and serve you, my
sister. Sister Lisa Marie, our sister,
she's at work today and she's asking us
to keep her in prayer. We are doing
that. Uh Sister Esther Lita White, we
love you. Uh you're dealing with some
hip and knee pain. We're praying the
Lord to touch and heal that today as
Sister Pauline prays for you. Sister
Leela, we're Sister Laya Peterson, we're
still praying for you and Wes. Praying
that Wes, he's on his third denial, but
God will make a way and open the door
for him to get that medication. Sister
Laya, just hold on. Hold on. Keep
trusting in Jesus. Amen. I pray that you
wake up in the middle of the night all
pain gone and don't need their
medication. Uh Sister Ava Monti, we're
praying for you uh that you uh uh will
be kind and loving and humble. Amen. All
of us need that. Sister praying for your
five children to find the Lord. That
your husband will lead as God leads.
that your mom's vision would remain and
that your sister will find the Lord.
We're praying for you. Praying for you,
mom, sister. Sister Regina B, we're
praying for your niece Madison's that
they will discover what's going on with
her hands. There's some issues there
with her hands. So, we're praying about
that. Um, Michael
uh, we're praying for Gabriel Pierce
who's, uh, now recovering from
postsurgery, but he's still at NYU
hospital. So, we're praying the Lord
will heal and touch him. And as you
know, we lost uh Sister Ginger entered
into her arrest uh this week. And so
we're praying for her family and
particularly brother Don who's grieving
over the loss of dear Ginger. And so
thank you, Sister Charlotte, for
reminding us of her. And thank you,
Sister Charlotte. It was because of you
that I got the opportunity to meet
Sister Ginger. And so uh such a
sweetheart. And uh we thank God for her
life and the memory of her. Brother Leon
is asking us to remember his sister Dean
in Miami, Florida. She had hip surgery
and after that hip surgery, she
developed an infection. So, we'll be
keeping all those prayer requests and
other prayer requests that we see going
up in the chat. Listen, we are always
pressed and wanting to cover all the
prayer requests, but there's just not
enough time. But because of that need
and that desire, uh, pastor has come up
with some wonderful ideas of some
wonderful ministries that we're going to
be doing. want to ask you to keep it in
prayer that about our new uh global
prayer channel that we're going to be
starting up and uh our living manner
prayer podcast. So, we're working on
some heavy stuff and we thank God for
it. God, get behind us and bless us and
touch it that we might be able to serve
you and get this word out and make the
make the truth known. And just know too,
if we were not able to share your praise
report live here, we have our prayer
warriors in the chat. They collect all
of your prayer requests. They are prayed
throughout the week and they will pray
with you live on the chat too. So, amen.
Thank you. And continue to put your
praise or I'm sorry, well, your praise
reports as well, but your prayer
requests in the chat and they will
collect those. And in fact, the sister
that's coming now to lead us in
intercessory prayer, her and her team, I
her and sister Christina, sister
Christina is so such a beautiful saint.
They work together and they disseminate
all the prayer requests throughout the
prayer warriors uh throughout the week
and each of us get you know a list of
prayer request to pray over all week and
it is this sister who's coming right now
sister Pauline Shimmo goodine is
responsible for that amongst other
duties and responsibilities in the
prayer ministry but she gonna come and
lead us to the altar. Come on and let
him use you sister. Hallelujah.
Hello Pauline.
Sister Pauline, you better come on off
mute now. Oh, we can't hear you.
Happy Sabbath. You hear me now? Sabbath.
There she is.
Amen. Yeah. I'm sitting up here looking
all angelical today. All with my wife.
So, you know, it's something. Yes, you
do.
Just something about Pauline. Terry and
I like to call Pauline special agent
Pauline because she knows how to ask all
the great questions. Yes. Yes, she
does. And thank y'all for that.
Amen.
But before I before I pray, uh the Holy
Spirit put this scripture on my heart.
So it's first Corinthians 13. We all
know it. We all know it. Amen. Father
God, the words my mouth and the
meditations of my heart be acceptable in
your sight. Oh Lord, our strength and
our redeemer. Amen.
Okay. Love
the though I speak with the tongues of
men and of angels and have not love, I
am becoming as a sounding brass or a
tinkling symbol. And though I have the
gift of prophecy and understand all
mysteries and all knowledge, and though
I have all faith so that I could remove
mountains and have not love, I am
nothing. And though I bestow all my
goods to feed the poor, and though I
give my body to be burned, and have not
love, it profited me nothing. Love
suffers long and it is kind. Love
envious not. Love walters not. It is not
puffed up. Does not behave itself
unseemly. Seek not his own. It is not
easily provoked. Thinketh no evil.
Rejoices not in iniquity, but rejoices
in the truth. Beth all things, believeth
all things, hope all things, endureth
all things. Love never faileth. But
whether there be prophecies, they shall
fail. Whether there be tongues, they
shall cease. Whether there be knowledge,
it shall vanish away. For we know in
part, and we prophesize in part. But
when that which is perfect is come, then
that which is in part shall be done
away. When I was a child, I spake as a
child. I understood as a child, I
thought as a child. But when I became a
man, I put away childish things. For now
we see through a
glass darkly, but then face to face. Now
I know in part, but then shall I know
even so also I am known. And now abideth
faith, hope, and love. These three, but
the greatest of these is love.
Amen. Amen.
Praise God. And um Sister White also,
she told us that we need to be reading
this chapter every day. Every day. Amen.
Because we going to need that love to
stay together to to fight this this good
fight that Jesus has given us the
strength to do it. Do not think that
y'all don't have strength. This right
here, here's your strength. Here is your
strength. Start reading it. Start using
it. Start saying it. start believing it
and then spread it to others because
that is what it's all about love. And if
you can't love and you and Ellen White
said it would bring us comfort and
strength but I'm going to add one more
thing this is not from Ellen White this
is for me give us forgiveness the
ability to forgive that is holding so
many of us back from that true love that
Christ want us to have in our hearts.
So, praise God for that. And if you
having trouble with that, with that love
and that forgiveness in your heart, look
to the
cross. Look to Jesus. Okay? He has
forgiven us cuz we put him on that
cross. We our sins. He died for us. So,
how dare that we do not forgive one
another. So, let's remember this. And
now I know my father is waiting for us
to go to the throne with with these
prayer requests, waiting happily,
anxiously. So let us bow our heads and
go to our father in prayer.
Father God, Father God, Lord Jesus, Holy
Spirit,
what a wonderful All your Sabbaths are
wonderful. Every last one of them.
Father God, we thank you that we are
even alive today. We are alive in our
right frame of mind. We are here
rejoicing. We just letting go
everything, Father God. And we just at
your feet. We are at your feet, Lord.
Just praising your name and thanking you
for everything you have done. We ask
you, Lord Jesus, to please clean us up
from the many sins we have committed.
Even today, somehow we desecrated your
Sabbath today in word, thought, and
deed. But we thank you that you have
forgiven us. You love us. Continue,
Father God, to answer our prayers.
Because if we don't confess our sins,
you will not answer. You will not even
hear. But we trust you, Lord. We trust
you with all our hearts that you will do
what you said that you would do for us,
Lord. Lord, some of us are just having
so many so much time with this so much
trouble just believing in you. But Lord,
we thank you. We thank you that you are
there. You are before the father. You
are holding up your hands, your nail
scarred hands. You are pleading for us,
Lord. Each person that is here today,
Lord, in your presence, you are talking
to the father and begging for us to be
forgiven of our sins. Now that we know
that we are, Lord, we thank you because
we believe you. You do not lie. You said
that if you confess, we confess our
sins, you are faithful and just to
forgive us of our sins and to cleanse us
from all
unrighteousness. Lord, now we could lift
up the many prayer requests that went
up. You you heard them all. You know
them all, Lord. There's so many that is
suffering from sickness, different
ailments, Father God. But you are the
greatest physician. You can heal, Father
God. But first of all, Father, we want
you to heal our hearts. We want you to
heal that. We want you to just take away
everything that we are doing, Father
God. Sometimes it's because we what we
do. That's why you have given us living
mana church Lord with health messages
and and everything that we need. But
Father God, we know that you will heal
all the people who is asking for
healings, Lord, from the top of their
heads to the soles of their feet. Father
God, you know some people are struggling
financially, Father God. And we know,
Father God, that you own everything.
Everything is yours, Lord. Just help us,
Lord, also to pay a faithful tithe and
offering because you promise in your
word that that that you told us to come
and and try you and see will you not
pour out our blessings upon us, Lord.
That is something that we also need to
look at father god within ourself. What
are we not doing? But father god we know
that you you love us and you want us to
understand that you are more than
willing more than able. You want to
answer all these prayers Lord and we
know that you will father God. We lift
up our families father God. So many of
us want our family members to be saved,
Lord. And Father God, you died. You died
for us, Lord Jesus. You shed your blood
for us. And you want nothing more than
for everybody to be saved. So, Father
God, we going to just keep praising you
and keep thanking you that our families
will be saved. Help us to be good and
faithful examples to them. Father God,
help us to live our lives, Lord, like
you. Help us to love. Help us to
continue to love one another. Help us to
forgive one another. And Lord, we know
marriages are also being tested, Lord.
Father God, you said that when two or
three are gathered in your name that you
are there. Father, just help them to
just turn to you. Help them to read the
um the the scriptures together. Help
them to study. Help them to come
together as a family, Lord, and just
lift your holy and magnificent name up,
Lord. Father God, these are trying times
and we are all going through something.
But, Father God, thank you so much for
helping us to stay together, bind us
together through the power of love and
to trust you through everything, oh
Lord. We know all these prayers will be
answered in the fullness of your time.
Help us not to give up. Help us to uh
stay strong. Help us to believe. Help us
not to be negative, talk negatively
always, Lord. You said through it all.
We are to trust you and believe in you
and praise through everything in our
lives. And Father God, now we're going
going to lift up your man, servant,
Pastor Myers. Father God, what a man of
God that he is. We thank you, Father
God, for pouring your Holy Spirit within
him. Thank you so much, Lord, that the
that the blessings that come out of his
mouth is from you and that we will all
give us all understanding. Give us all
listening ears to listen closely to what
the spirit is going to um say to us
through Pastor Meyers. So, we thank you
so much, Lord. Thank you so much for
hearing and answering this prayer. And
anything that we fail to ask, Lord,
please fail not to grant in Jesus' name.
Amen.
Amen. Amen.
Praise the Lord.
M
God and God
[Music]
alone created
all these things we
call our
own. From the mighty to the small,